export const AccordionData = [
    {
        "Question": "What is PaisaPay?",
        "Answer": "PaisaPay is a peer-to-peer (P2P) payment service that allows individuals to easily send and receive money from friends, family, or anyone else. It offers a seamless and secure platform for hassle-free financial transactions."
    },
    {
        "Question": "How do I sign up for PaisaPay?",
        "Answer": "Signing up for PaisaPay is simple. Visit our website, create an account using your email or phone number, and follow the prompts to set up your profile and link your preferred payment methods."
    },
    {
        "Question": "Is PaisaPay secure?",
        "Answer": "Absolutely. We prioritize the security of your financial information. Our platform utilizes state-of-the-art encryption and rigorous security measures to ensure that your transactions are safe and protected."
    },
    {
        "Question": " Can I use PaisaPay for business transactions?",
        "Answer": "Currently, PaisaPay is designed for personal peer-to-peer transactions. We are actively exploring options to expand our services to accommodate business transactions in the future."
    },
    {
        "Question": "Are there any fees for using PaisaPay?",
        "Answer": "Using PaisaPay is generally free for standard P2P transactions. However, there may be nominal fees for certain services or premium features. Please refer to our fee schedule for detailed information."
    },
    {
        "Question": "How quickly do payments through PaisaPay reach the recipient?",
        "Answer": "Most transactions through PaisaPay are processed instantly. However, some factors, such as bank processing times, may affect the exact timing of the recipient receiving the funds."
    },
    {
        "Question": "Can I send money internationally with PaisaPay?",
        "Answer": "Currently, PaisaPay primarily supports domestic transactions. We are actively exploring options to expand our services to include international money transfers in the future."
    },
    {
        "Question": "What happens if I send money to the wrong recipient?",
        "Answer": "PaisaPay encourages users to double-check recipient details before confirming transactions. In the event of an error, please contact our customer support for assistance, and we will do our best to help resolve the issue."
    },
    {
        "Question": "How do I contact PaisaPay's customer support?",
        "Answer": "You can reach our dedicated customer support team through the 'Help' section on our website. We're here to assist you with any questions or concerns you may have."
    },
    {
        "Question": " Can I set up recurring payments with PaisaPay?",
        "Answer": "Currently, PaisaPay does not support recurring payments. However, we are actively exploring options to expand our services to include this feature in the future."
    },
    {
        "Question": "Is PaisaPay available on all devices?",
        "Answer": "Yes, PaisaPay is accessible through both web browsers, making it convenient for you to manage your payments on your preferred device."
    }
]